[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Christmas"]}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "What is the purpose of Christmas?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "purpose", "of", "Christmas", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Well, you know, the angels in the story of the first Christmas said three things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "angels", "in", "the", "story", "of", "the", "first", "Christmas", "said", "three", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "And do you get people from all religions?", "question_tokens": ["And", "do", "you", "get", "people", "from", "all", "religions", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Oh, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "-- or a Jew or whoever it may be?", "question_tokens": ["--", "or", "a", "Jew", "or", "whoever", "it", "may", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "JJR", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Well, we're an overtly Christian church.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "'re", "an", "overtly", "Christian", "church", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "But why do you think it's on the decline?", "question_tokens": ["But", "why", "do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "on", "the", "decline", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Well, I think there are three different factors.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "there", "are", "three", "different", "factors", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Do you like the extraordinary position of responsibility you now have -- now have for yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "the", "extraordinary", "position", "of", "responsibility", "you", "now", "have", "--", "now", "have", "for", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "I don't say that I like it, but I try to use it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "say", "that", "I", "like", "it", ",", "but", "I", "try", "to", "use", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "-- is it healthy?", "question_tokens": ["--", "is", "it", "healthy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Well, no, it's not healthy.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "no", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "healthy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "And they then devote a large chunk of that to helping needy people, people less fortunate than themselves, does that balance it out?", "question_tokens": ["And", "they", "then", "devote", "a", "large", "chunk", "of", "that", "to", "helping", "needy", "people", ",", "people", "less", "fortunate", "than", "themselves", ",", "does", "that", "balance", "it", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "TO", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "ARREN: Well, the studies show, no, it doesn't.", "answer_tokens": ["ARREN", ":", "Well", ",", "the", "studies", "show", ",", "no", ",", "it", "does", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "Have you had big problems in that marriage, if you like?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "big", "problems", "in", "that", "marriage", ",", "if", "you", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "Do people give up on marriage too early these days?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "people", "give", "up", "on", "marriage", "too", "early", "these", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", ":", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "They don't fight enough for it?", "question_tokens": ["They", "do", "n't", "fight", "enough", "for", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Well, and -- and the problem is, you're an imperfect person and you're going to marry an imperfect person.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "and", "--", "and", "the", "problem", "is", ",", "you", "'re", "an", "imperfect", "person", "and", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "marry", "an", "imperfect", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "have", "you", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "Rick, how many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "question_tokens": ["Rick", ",", "how", "many", "times", "have", "you", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "Well, probably in my teenage years, I fell in love every week.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "probably", "in", "my", "teenage", "years", ",", "I", "fell", "in", "love", "every", "week", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "-- it feels completely natural?", "question_tokens": ["--", "it", "feels", "completely", "natural", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "Oh, it's not only natural, it's euphoric.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "only", "natural", ",", "it", "'s", "euphoric", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "What -- why can you not allow them to have that euphoria that you had, with all the rights that go with that kind of relationship?", "question_tokens": ["What", "--", "why", "can", "you", "not", "allow", "them", "to", "have", "that", "euphoria", "that", "you", "had", ",", "with", "all", "the", "rights", "that", "go", "with", "that", "kind", "of", "relationship", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Great question.", "answer_tokens": ["Great", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "Can I pull that back?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "pull", "that", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "-- supporting and voting and making legal gay marriage?", "question_tokens": ["--", "supporting", "and", "voting", "and", "making", "legal", "gay", "marriage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 507, "question": "-- it is just wrong?", "question_tokens": ["--", "it", "is", "just", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Well...", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Or could you see a time when you may say, you know something, America has changed, I'm prepared to change?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "could", "you", "see", "a", "time", "when", "you", "may", "say", ",", "you", "know", "something", ",", "America", "has", "changed", ",", "I", "'m", "prepared", "to", "change", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "I don't see that happening, because I have a world view based on scripture that remains unchanged.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "see", "that", "happening", ",", "because", "I", "have", "a", "world", "view", "based", "on", "scripture", "that", "remains", "unchanged", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "NN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 559, "question": "What does being free mean?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "being", "free", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "No, no, nobody -- you can love anybody you want to in our freedom...", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "nobody", "--", "you", "can", "love", "anybody", "you", "want", "to", "in", "our", "freedom", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "But what is freedom?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "is", "freedom", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 581, "question": "Is that if -- if a mean -- a word means a certain thing, and it's not -- and it's not my word and all of a sudden I say, well, I'm that, is that fair?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "if", "--", "if", "a", "mean", "--", "a", "word", "means", "a", "certain", "thing", ",", "and", "it", "'s", "not", "--", "and", "it", "'s", "not", "my", "word", "and", "all", "of", "a", "sudden", "I", "say", ",", "well", ",", "I", "'m", "that", ",", "is", "that", "fair", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "You...", "answer_tokens": ["You", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "So you wouldn't have amended anything to the Constitution?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "would", "n't", "have", "amended", "anything", "to", "the", "Constitution", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "I'm -- I'm not sure what you're saying.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "sure", "what", "you", "'re", "saying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bible", "Bible", "Bible", "Bible"]}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", ":", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "You think everything in the Bible is completely accurate?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "everything", "in", "the", "Bible", "is", "completely", "accurate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "I think the Bible is true; not everything in the Bible that is explained in the Bible does the Bible commend.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "Bible", "is", "true", ";", "not", "everything", "in", "the", "Bible", "that", "is", "explained", "in", "the", "Bible", "does", "the", "Bible", "commend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bible"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 670, "question": "How do you try and change the fact that Christmas becomes this crystallization for many people of all that's terrible in their lives?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "try", "and", "change", "the", "fact", "that", "Christmas", "becomes", "this", "crystallization", "for", "many", "people", "of", "all", "that", "'s", "terrible", "in", "their", "lives", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 671, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Birthday Party for Jesus"]}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "It is a tradition we call Birthday Party for Jesus.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "a", "tradition", "we", "call", "Birthday", "Party", "for", "Jesus", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "Do you know how much you're worth?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "much", "you", "'re", "worth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 760, "question": "He's an impressive guy, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "an", "impressive", "guy", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 761, "answer": "He is.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 768, "question": "How do you combine diet with prayer?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "combine", "diet", "with", "prayer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 769, "answer": "Well, it's funny how this thing started, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "funny", "how", "this", "thing", "started", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 801, "question": "So what are the key things you have to do with this diet?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "are", "the", "key", "things", "you", "have", "to", "do", "with", "this", "diet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 802, "answer": "The number one thing -- you know, of course, diets are diets and health plans are health plans.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "number", "one", "thing", "--", "you", "know", ",", "of", "course", ",", "diets", "are", "diets", "and", "health", "plans", "are", "health", "plans", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 833, "question": "You drink alcohol?", "question_tokens": ["You", "drink", "alcohol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 834, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 836, "question": "Never had (INAUDIBLE) nip, not even at Christmas?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "had", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "nip", ",", "not", "even", "at", "Christmas", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 837, "answer": "Never have.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 848, "question": "What would you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 849, "answer": "Well, the message of Christmas is that that babe in the manger didn't stay a babe in the manger.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "message", "of", "Christmas", "is", "that", "that", "babe", "in", "the", "manger", "did", "n't", "stay", "a", "babe", "in", "the", "manger", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]